<sect1 id="config-mouse">
  <title>Mouse</title>
  <sect2 id="mouse-config-introduction">
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <para>
      The mouse capplet in the <application>GNOME Control
	Center</application> helps to configure properties of the mouse,
      such as: whether you're left handed or right handed, sensitivity,
      and mouse speed.
    </para>
  </sect2>
  <sect2 id="config-mouse-buttons">
    <title>The Buttons Tab</title>
    <para>
      The buttons tab controls properties for the mouse buttons.
    </para>      
    <sect3 id="config-mouse-buttons-orientation">
      <title>Mouse Orientation</title>
      <para>
	A mouse behaves differently based on whether the user is right
	or left handed.  If they're right handed, the left button is the
	action button, while the right button is the menu button.  The
	mouse also typically sits on the right hand side of the desk.
	If the user is left handed, they use the right button as the
	action button, while the left button is the menu button.  It
	also sits on the left hand of the desk.
      </para>
      <para>
	To configure the hand orientation, select the
	<guibutton>Left-handed mouse</guibutton> button.  If you're
	right handed, deselect that button.  Press
	<guibutton>Apply</guibutton> to apply your changes.
      </para>
    </sect3>
    <sect3 id="config-mouse-buttons-dclick">
      <title>Double-click Delay</title>
      <para>
	Double-clicking speed can be configured, to let you set how
	fast you want to double-click.  This can be good for disabled
	people who can't click fast.
      </para>
      <para>
	Select the delay you wish to use on the slider.  The more
	right it is, the longer the delay allowed.
      </para>
      <para>
	You can test the speed by double-clicking on the cake at
	right.  The candle will light on fire if it detected a
	double-click.
      </para>
    </sect3>
  </sect2>
  <sect2 id="config-mouse-cursors">
    <title>The Mouse Cursors Tab</title>
    <para>
      Cursors are the part on the desktop that represents where the
      mouse is.  The cursor can be changed for easier use.
    </para>
    <sect3 id="config-mouse-cursors-theme">
      <title>Cursor Themes</title>
      <para>
	<application>Gnome</application>'s mouse cursors can be
	configured to look different.  For example, if you have a dark
	desktop, you may want to use the white cursor.
      </para>
      <para>
	To select a theme, simply click the theme you wish to use and
	click <guibutton>Apply</guibutton>.  You will need to logout
	for this change to occur.
      </para>
    </sect3>
    <sect3 id="config-mouse-cursors-locate">
      <title>Locating Cursors Option</title>
      <para>
	Sometimes, you'll lose where the cursor is.  If you select the
	<guibutton>Show position of cursor when the Control key is
	pressed</guibutton>, the cursor will be animated when you
	press and release the control key.
      </para>
    </sect3>
  </sect2>
  <sect2 id="config-mouse-motion">
    <title>The Motion Tab</title>
    <para>
      The mouse cursor can be set to move at different speeds and
      sensitivities.  The following options are available for you to
      edit:
    </para>
    <sect3 id="config-mouse-motion-speed">
      <title>Speed</title>
      <para>
	The mouse pointer can move at different speeds across the
	screen.  Everyone has their favorite speed, so the ability to
	configure this is important.
      </para>
<!-- Figure out what acceleration and sensitivity is -->
      <para>
	To set your mouse speed, move the bar to either faster or slower
	in the <guilabel>Mouse speed</guilabel> section.  Afterwards,
	click <guibutton>Apply</guibutton> to test the speed.  Once you
	select your desired speed, click <guibutton>Close</guibutton>.
      </para>
    </sect3>
    <sect3 id="config-mouse-motion-dnd">
      <title>Drag and Drop</title>
      <para>
	Drag and drop is clicking an object, and dragging it to
	another place on the screen, causing an event to occur.
      </para>
      <para>
	You need to drag it a certain amount of distance before the
	system will recognize it as a drag and drop operation.  To
	configure how far to drag it, move the slider left or right.
      </para>
    </sect3>
  </sect2>
</sect1>
